-What's up? -I left my guitar here.
-怎麼了？ -我忘了拿吉他
Okay. No problem.
好吧，沒問題
Okay. Here you go.
拿去吧
-What? -You want to hang out or something?
-什麼？ -你要聊聊嗎？
You caught me at a bad time.
你來的不是時候
-Are you and Chandler..? -Exactly.
-你跟錢德… -沒錯
-Can I play for you? -No.
-要我幫你們伴奏嗎？ -不必
Hey, Pheebs, what's up?
菲比，你好嗎？
You ask an intriguing question, Chandler Bing.
你問了一個很有趣的問題 錢德賓
Oh, my God! You're getting a massage? You never let me massage you.
天啊，你請人幫你按摩？ 你從來不讓我幫你按摩
Phoebe, I can explain.
菲比，我可以解釋
You see..
聽著…
God, I gotta get better at lying.
天啊，我得學怎麼說謊
You said you hate massages.
你說過你討厭按摩
Buy stamps. Pick up dry cleaning. Don't let Phoebe in.
去買郵票，拿乾洗的衣服 別讓菲比進來
How long has this been going on?
你背著我這麼做多久了？
-Well, Alexandra has.. -It has a name?
-亞麗珊卓… -它還有名字？
Phoebe, don't get upset.
菲比，別生氣
Okay. Oh, too late! I'm leaving. Come on, Chandler, let's go.
好吧，太遲了，我要走了 來吧，錢德，我們走
Well, I thought I'd..
我以為我…
Yeah, what the hell.
對，管它的
The One With The Secret Closet
本集播出：秘密衣櫃
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
One more push. Come on, we're almost there.
再推一次 加油，快好了
I'm happy things worked out for us and we're having this baby. I love you.
我很高興我們能在一起 我們要生孩子了，我愛你
I love you too.
我也愛你
I hope it's not an inappropriate time to say..
我希望現在說這個 不會不是時候…
you're the best sex I've ever had.
你是我最棒的性伴侶
That's always appropriate.
你隨時都能那麼說
Okay, come on, one more push. One more push.
來吧，再推一次 再推一次
There we go.
好了
Here is your beautiful baby. Congratulations.
你們的漂亮寶寶 恭喜
I hope you're a better father than you are a friend!
希望你做爸爸 比做朋友稱職
Joey!
喬伊
-What's going on? -Come feel my belly.
-發生了什麼事？ -快來摸摸我的肚子
-The baby's kicking for the first time. -Really?
-這是寶寶第一次踢我 -真的嗎？
Yes.
對
You know what? Maybe you..
你知道嗎？或許你…
Maybe you should come to me. I'm not wearing any bottoms.
或許你該走過來 我沒有穿褲子
Oh, my God.
天啊
It's unbelievable!
太不可思議了
Wow, she is kicking so much. She's like..
她踢得好厲害 她像是…
Who's that annoying girl soccer player?
那個討厭的 女足球員是誰？
-Mia Hamm? -Mia Hamm!
-米亞漢姆？ -米亞漢姆
-It's amazing. -One hand on the sheet, Joe.
-太神奇了 -抓住你的床單，喬伊
Sorry.
抱歉
Hey, babe.
嘿，寶貝
We got a wedding gift from Bob and Faye Bing. They don't like us, do they?
巴伯跟菲伊賓送我們結婚禮物 他們不喜歡我們，對吧？
Who says you can't get a nice punch bowl for under $6?
誰說買不到 六塊以下的高級雞尾酒碗？
-Maybe we can take it back. -Where would we return it?
-或許我們能把它退回去 -我們要把它退到哪裡去？
How about to the street, from the balcony?
何不從陽台 把它丟到街上？
We can't do that. What if they come by for a visit?
我們不能那麼做 萬一他們來看我們呢？
Let's cross that bridge when my aunt and uncle who I haven't seen in 15 years..
我們過橋去看 我15年沒看過的阿姨跟姨丈…
drop by unexpectedly and demand a giant bowl of punch.
給他們一個驚喜 要他們送我們大一點的雞尾酒碗
Why don't we just find a place for it?
我們為什麼不找個地方放它？
In that cabinet?
放在那個櫃子裡？
That's for canned goods. Have you forgotten everything from orientation?
那是放罐頭食物的 你忘了每樣東西都要放在定位嗎？
How about the closet by the bathroom?
浴室旁邊的櫃子呢？
-Okay. Let me do it. -No, I'll do it.
-讓我來吧 -不，我來就行了
You have to relax and let me take care of things once in a while.
你得放輕鬆 偶爾把事情交給我來做
It's locked. You have to help me. Why is it locked?
上鎖了，你得幫幫我 為什麼上鎖了？
No reason. I keep private things in there.
沒有為什麼 我把私人物品放在那裡
I've been here a while, and I've never seen what's in there.
我搬到這裡來一陣子了 從來沒看過裡面的東西
What is in there?
裡面放了什麼？
Feminine stuff.
女人的東西
Don't try to make me uncomfortable with feminine stuff!
別想用女人的東西 來唬我
Nothing in there concerns you. If you love me, you'll just let it go.
那裡面沒有你喜歡的東西 如果你愛我，忘了這件事
-Fine. -Thank you.
-好吧 -謝謝
Love you.
我愛你
Hello, Chandler. Lovely day, huh? You.
錢德 今天天氣真好，是你
If it helps, Alexandra's only been massaging her for three years.
如果有幫助的話 亞麗珊卓已經幫她按摩了三年
If! I said, if it helps.
我說如果有幫助的話
Why won't you let me massage you?
你為什麼不讓我幫你按摩？
I'd be self-conscious. You're my friend. I'd be naked.
我會無法放鬆 你是我的朋友，我得脫光衣服
We lived together for years. I've seen you naked.
我們住在一起那麼多年 我看過你沒穿衣服
That's different. We were roommates. And when?
那不一樣，我們是室友 那是什麼時候的事？
I'm curious about the human body.
我對人體很好奇
You can understand why this would be weird.
你可以瞭解 為什麼我會覺得很奇怪
I'm a professional and I'm really good.
我是專家 我真的很厲害
If you're uncomfortable, we can stop. Give me a chance. Please?
如果你覺得不舒服，我們就停止 給我一個機會，拜託
If it means that much to you.
如果你真的覺得很重要
It does. How would you feel if you couldn't share your cooking?
沒錯，如果你無法分享你的廚藝 你會有什麼感覺？
Or how Ross would feel if he couldn't teach us about dragons.
如果羅斯沒辦法教我們龍的事 他會有什麼感覺？
-Dinosaurs. -Potato, potahto.
-是恐龍 -都一樣
Ross, the baby's kicking.
羅斯，寶寶在踢
What? It is?
什麼？是嗎？
It's not kicking now.
她現在沒有在踢我
Although we would love to see you do that again.
雖然我們很想 看到你再做一次
When? What happened?
什麼時候？發生了什麼事？
Last night. I went into Joey's room, and he was sleeping.
昨晚我跑到喬伊的房間 他在睡覺
A dreamless sleep.
我沒有做夢
My God, the baby's kicking. That's great.
天啊，寶寶會踢了 真的是太棒了
I wish I would have been there to feel the kicking for the first time.
我希望我可以摸到 寶寶第一次踢你的樣子
I got some stuff going on if you want to feel.
如果你真的想摸 我的肚子正在咕咕叫
I'll pass, but you look radiant.
我不要，但你看起來有母性光輝
I don't want to miss any more baby stuff. Here's my pager number.
我不想再錯過寶寶的事了 這是我新的呼叫器號碼
Anytime anything pregnancy-related happens, use it.
只要發生跟懷孕有關的事 立刻通知我
I don't care if it's 3 a.m. and you want ice cream.
我不在乎那是凌晨三點 而你想吃冰淇淋
Can I get a copy of that?
我能抄一份嗎？
-Are you under the sheet? -Yes.
-你裹著床單嗎？ -對
Great, let's begin.
好了，我們開始吧
How's the pressure?
力道還可以吧？
It's nice. Wow, Phoebe, you are good.
很不錯，菲比，你真的很厲害
Stating the obvious, but thank you.
很明顯，謝謝你的誇獎
-And it's not weird, is it? -No.
-那一點都不奇怪，對吧？ -沒錯
That's right, you just enjoy.
沒錯，好好享受吧
Oh, yeah!
對
-Oh, yeah! -Okay.
-對 -好吧
Oh, God, Phoebe!
天啊，菲比
That's it! That's it, right there!
就是那樣，就是那裡
I wasn't trying to open your closet, I swear.
我發誓 我沒有試著打開你的櫃子
Monica runs a pretty tight ship here, doesn't she? What are you doing?
摩妮卡管你很嚴，對吧？ 你在做什麼？
Monica has a secret closet. She won't let me see it.
摩妮卡有秘密衣櫃 她不肯讓我看它
-Why not? -I don't know! What's she hiding?
-為什麼？ -我不知道，她在隱瞞什麼？
I don't know.
我不知道
I bet it's Richard.
我敢說是理查
-What? -Before you say I'm wrong..
-什麼？ -在你說我錯了之前…
let me ask you something.
我要問你一件事
When was the last time you saw him?
你最後一次看到他是什麼時候的事？
Why would she keep Richard in here?
她為什麼要把理查關在那裡？
Off the top of my head..
我不知道…
maybe she's having her cake and eating it too.
或者她想魚與熊掌兼得
You being the "cake, " Richard being the "too."
你是「熊掌」 理查只是「魚」
-That was off the top of your head? -Yeah.
-那就是你想出來的理論？ -對
-Or.. -And here we go.
-或是… -又來了
I saw a movie where there was a door. Nobody knew what was behind it.
我看過一部電影裡有一扇門 沒有人知道裡面藏了什麼
When they finally got it open, millions of bugs came pouring out..
最後他們把門打開後 好幾百萬隻蟲跑了出來…
and they feasted on human flesh!
他們會吃人肉
It wouldn't kill you to respect your wife's privacy!
尊重你老婆的隱私 不會要你的命
Stupid closet full of bugs!
塞滿蟲的笨衣櫃
Joey, something feels weird and not good weird. I don't..
喬伊，我覺得怪怪的 那不是好事，我不…
When my sisters were pregnant..
我妹妹懷孕時…
they got weird feelings and it was always nothing.
她們都覺得怪怪的 結果根本沒事
-Really? -Absolutely.
-真的嗎？ -當然
But we'll stop by the hospital just to be sure. I'll page Ross.
但我們得到醫院檢查一下 我會呼叫羅斯
Rach, look at me. Everything's fine. Trust me. Take my hand. Here we go.
瑞秋，看著我，一切都會沒事的 相信我，握著我的手，我們走吧
Crushing bones!
我快骨折了
Good thing we're going to a hospital.
還好我們要去醫院
-Open it. -Why'd you..
-打開它 -你為什麼…
Watch your feet. There's bugs everywhere.
小心你的腳 到處都有蟲
-So? -She's fine.
-結果呢？ -她沒事
She had Braxton Hicks contractions. Mild discomfort in the uterine wall.
她出現不規則的子宮收縮 那是子宮壁出現中度不適的現象
Mild discomfort? I take it you've had one of these Braxton thingies?
中度不適？ 我想你也出現過那種現象
-Everything's normal? -Yes.
-一切都很正常？ -對
-There's no danger? -No.
-沒有危險？ -對
Contractions can be unnerving, but she's fine.
收縮雖然會不舒服 但她沒事
Thank you, doctor. And thank you for being nice and calm.
謝謝你，醫生 謝謝你這麼溫和冷靜
I wasn't calm! I've never been more scared in my life.
我一點都不冷靜 我從來沒有這麼害怕過
-You said everything was okay. -What do I know? I'm not a doctor.
-你說一切都會沒事的 -我知道什麼？我不是醫生
-But everything is okay. I'm fine. -You sure?
-但一切都沒事，我沒事 -你確定？
Yes. I got half a mind to contract that doctor's uterus.
對，我真希望 那個醫生的子宮也會收縮
Mild discomfort! What's he talking about?
中度不適 他到底在胡說什麼？
-Is everything okay? -Yes.
-沒事吧？ -沒事
Your page said, "Come to the hospital." What happened?
你呼叫我說「趕到醫院來」 發生了什麼事？
Something called Braxton Hicks contraction.
她出現不規則的子宮收縮
That's no big deal. Most women don't feel them.
那沒什麼大不了的 很多女人都不會有感覺
No uterus, no opinion.
沒有子宮的人不能置評
What's with the candy?
糖果是怎麼一回事？
I was at the concession stand at the movies.
你呼叫我時 我在電影院買零食
-You went to the movies by yourself? -Mona!
-你自己去看電影？ -蒙娜
-I gotta go back in there. -What's wrong?
-我得回檢查室去 -發生了什麼事？
-I just gotta.. -No, really, tell me. What's up?
-我得… -不，告訴我，怎麼了？
Look, I forgot my underwear.
聽著，我忘了穿內褲
Thanks for bringing her to the hospital.
謝謝你送她來醫院
Don't worry about it. No big deal.
別擔心，那沒有什麼大不了的
But still, it should have been me. I'm the dad.
但應該是由我送她來 我是孩子的爸
-Here's information on Braxton Hicks. -Thanks.
-這是不規則收縮的資料 -謝謝
You did the right thing by bringing her in.
你送她過來是對的
You'll make a wonderful father.
你會是個好爸爸
Hey, not as good as this guy. He brought Twizzlers.
我沒有這傢伙厲害 他買了糖果
-There has got to be a way. -Easy there, Captain Kirk.
-一定會有辦法 -別緊張，寇克船長
-Do you have a bobby pin? -Yeah.
-你有小別針嗎？ -有
Oh, no, wait. I'm not a 9-year-old girl.
不，等一下 我不是九歲的小女孩
Then why do you throw like one?
為什麼你投球的時候很像？
-Maybe Monica has a bobby pin. -Oh, sure, "Monica."
-或許摩妮卡有小別針 -對，「摩妮卡」
So how's the inappropriate crush on Rachel coming?
你暗戀瑞秋的事 怎麼樣了？
Really good. I should be ready to kill myself any day now.
真的很不錯 我應該隨時準備好自殺
Well, you sure found that quick.
你這麼快就發現了
I wish I didn't feel this way about Rachel. I wish things could be normal.
我希望我從沒有愛過瑞秋 我希望一切能恢復正常
I love living with her, and helping out with the baby is amazing.
我喜歡跟她一起住 幫助她生產真的很有趣
But now I think Ross feels left out.
但我覺得羅斯覺得自己被排除在外
When I took Rachel to the hospital, the doctor thought I was the father.
我送瑞秋去醫院時 醫生以為我是孩子的爸
You should have seen the look on Ross' face.
你應該看看羅斯的表情
I have no idea what I'm doing. For all I know, I'm locking it more.
我不知道我在做什麼 我只知道我越開鎖得越緊
-You try opening it with a credit card? -That's a good idea.
-你想拿信用卡打開它嗎？ -好點子
So Ross is kind of bummed, huh?
羅斯很難過？
-I feel terrible. -It's not your fault.
-我覺得很難過 -那不是你的錯
What are you gonna do, not take her? You're doing nothing wrong.
你要怎麼做？不送她去醫院？ 你沒有做錯事
Except for harboring love for the woman carrying his baby.
但你不該愛上 懷了他孩子的女人
Well, there is that.
好了
Richard, if you're in there, could you pass me my credit card?
理查，如果你在裡面 麻煩你把信用卡還我
I gotta tell you, yesterday was amazing. That massage felt so good.
我得告訴你昨天真的很棒 按摩感覺很舒服
No, I got that.
不，我瞭解
-Can we make it a weekly appointment? -Okay.
-我們能每星期按摩一次嗎？ -好吧
You should know though, I've raised my rates to $200 an hour.
但你應該知道 我的時薪調成兩百塊了
-Okay. -I mean 500.
-好吧 -我是說五百塊
-What? -600.
-什麼？ -六百塊
What's going on?
怎麼回事？
You make sex noises when you get massaged.
我按摩你時 你會發出性愛叫聲
It freaked me out. After a while, I tried to hurt you. It spurred you on.
那把我嚇壞了 之後我想弄痛你，你叫得更大聲
You're crazy. There's nothing sexual about the noises I make.
你瘋了 我的叫聲一點都不淫蕩
There's nothing sexual about this?
這一點都不淫蕩？
Oh, God!
天啊
What are you looking at?
你在看什麼？
I mean, hi.
我是說，嗨
Oh, that's why Alexandra wears earplugs when she gives me a massage.
所以亞麗珊卓幫我按摩時 都會戴耳塞
It's not because she hates Enya.
那不是因為她討厭恩雅
This is embarrassing. I'm never getting a massage again.
這真的是太丟臉了 我永遠都不會再按摩了
Don't let this stop you from getting massages.
別讓這件事 害你放棄按摩
I have lots of clients that make those noises.
我有很多客人 也會發出那種叫聲
-Really? -Well, not clients. Lovers.
-真的嗎？ -他們不是客人，他們是情人
We'll try it again. Come back, and we'll work through it.
我們再試一次 再來找我，我們會想出辦法的
-You sure? -Yes.
-你確定？ -對
-I guess. -Great! Now, if you'll just excuse me.
-我猜是吧 -太棒了，對不起
So did you hear something you liked?
你聽到你喜歡的聲音了嗎？
Hey, Ross, check it out! I learned a new trick.
羅斯，你看 我學到新把戲了
You know, if you stick one hand down your pants, you're the spitting image of Joey.
如果一隻手放在褲袋裡 你和喬伊沒兩樣
Hey, I brought you some lunch.
我幫你買了午餐
Oh, that's so sweet of you. Oh, yum.
你真的太貼心了，真好吃
-Did you put pickles on this? -Well, yeah.
-你放了醃黃瓜嗎？ -對
What? What? Rach, what?
什麼？瑞秋，怎麼了？
-What's going on? -I made her tuna with pickle.
-發生了什麼事？ -我幫她帶了醃黃瓜魷魚三明治
Pickle? Pickle makes her sick.
醃黃瓜？那會讓她想吐
Giving her pickle is like giving me salad.
讓她吃醃黃瓜就像讓我吃沙拉
I'm sorry, I didn't know. You okay?
抱歉，我不知道，你還好嗎？
I'm fine, but someone make sure it's gone when I get out?
我沒事，但我不在的時候 麻煩誰解決掉它
I'm on it!
我在吃了
I shouldn't be the one making her throw up.
我不該讓她吐的
-lt could happen to anyone. -Not to you. You know this stuff.
-誰都可以做出這種事 -你就不會，你瞭解她
I don't know any of it and I'm the father.
我什麼都不懂，而我是孩子的爸
I wish I could be more involved, you know?
我希望我能多參與一點
Well, if anyone is keeping score, I no longer eat tuna.
如果有人在幫我紀錄的話 我絕不會再吃魷魚了
Can I talk to you guys for a second?
我能跟你們談一談嗎？
-Yeah. -What's up?
-可以啊 -怎麼了？
Sit down. I wanna talk about our situation.
坐吧 我想談談我們的情況
Are you breaking up with us?
你要跟我們分手嗎？
The thing is..
我要說的是…
because I live with Rachel, I'm here for a lot of stuff.
因為我跟瑞秋一起住 我參與了很多事
And Ross is missing everything. So..
羅斯錯過了一切，所以…
Yeah?
怎麼了？
You two should live together.
你們兩個應該住在一起
Are you asking me to move? You don't want me here?
你要我搬出來？ 你不要我住在這裡？
No, I love living with you. It just seems that..
不，我喜歡跟你一起住 只不過…
if you're gonna have a roommate, it may as well be the father.
如果你需要室友 他最好是孩子的爸
But, Joey, I don't think Ross wants me to move in and disrupt his life.
喬伊，我想羅斯不希望 我搬過去干擾他的生活
Or he does.
或許他想那麼做
I would love to be around for you and the baby.
我很樂意 照顧你跟寶寶
We can just try it, like on a temporary basis.
我們可試試看 先試一陣子
-But it's you and me. -lt wouldn't be anything romantic.
-但那是你跟我 -我們不會有感情牽扯
I'm dating Mona. Damn it, Mona!
我在和蒙娜交往，該死，蒙娜
I was supposed to meet her an hour ago. What is wrong with me?
我跟她約好一小時前要見面 我是怎麼了？
So, what do you think?
你們覺得呢？
Living with the father of the baby. It's a little conventional for us.
跟孩子的爸住在一起 對我們來說那太傳統了
Yeah, but hey, hey. You always have liked my building.
對，但是 你一直都喜歡我的公寓
And there's more room. I mean, you could have a closet dedicated to shoes.
我還有空房間 你還會有放鞋專櫃
Oh, you do know your audience.
你真的很瞭解你的聽眾
-I don't know. Is it crazy? -No.
-我不知道，那很瘋狂嗎？ -不
Joey, this is a smart idea.
喬伊，這是個聰明點子
Well, I was due.
我該想到的
-Let's do it. -Really?
-就這麼辦吧 -真的嗎？
Rach, that's great. That's great.
瑞秋，那真的是太棒了
And you know what? Don't worry about any of the moving.
你知道嗎？ 別擔心搬家的事
I'll take care of everything. In fact, I'll start right now.
一切都交給我 事實上我會從現在開始幫你搬家
Ross, Ross. Mona?
羅斯，蒙娜
Unbelievable.
不可思議
Not too shabby. I got this all off myself..
還不錯 我用我太太的工具…
using my wife's tools.
把自己弄成這個樣子
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
How did you get in there?
你怎麼把它打開的？
You're messy.
你很不整潔
-No! You weren't supposed to see this! -I married Fred Sanford.
-不，你不該看到這個的 -我娶了收集狂
Chandler, you don't understand.
錢德，你不瞭解
You know, how I organize everything, right?
你知道 我喜歡把東西排得整整齊齊的
Okay, well this is all of the stuff that doesn't fit into any category.
這些是我無法分類的東西
So you see, I'm not messy.
我不是懶散的太太
I'm just so organized that..
我太講究了，所以…
Okay, okay, fine! Now you know. I'm sick.
好吧，現在你知道了 我很病態
No, honey, you're not sick. I don't love you because you're organized.
不，親愛的，你不病態 我愛你不是因為你做事有條不紊
I love you in spite of that.
不論如何，我都愛你
Really?
真的嗎？
-Promise you won't tell anyone? -Yes.
-你發誓不會告訴任何人？ -對
Now that I know, if I've got extra stuff, can we share the closet?
現在我知道了，如果我有多餘的東西 我們可以一起用那個櫃子嗎？
Well.. It's just..
喔…那只是…
I'm afraid you might mess it up.
我怕你會把它弄亂
-Hey. -Hey.
-嘿 -嘿
So Rachel's all moved out? How you taking it?
瑞秋搬出去了？ 你還好吧？
I wanted to have a few beers..
我要喝幾瓶啤酒…
but I got rid of those because Rachel couldn't stand the smell.
但我把啤酒都丟了 因為瑞秋受不了那個味道
I have thrown back a lot of orange juice with calcium.
我買了很多 加鈣的柳橙汁
It's a couple weeks past its expiration date, so it's got a bit of a kick.
它已經過期了幾星期 所以會有點酸味
-Are you okay? -You kidding me? Yeah, I'm great.
-你沒事吧？ -你在開玩笑嗎？我棒透了
I'm better than great. I am good.
我好到不能再好，我很好
Now that she's gone, I can do stuff around here that I couldn't do before.
現在她離開了 我可以做以前不能做的事
Like..
譬如…
I can walk around naked again.
我又能脫光衣服亂跑了
I can..
我可以…
I can watch porn in the living room.
我可以在客廳看色情片
This is good for me.
這對我來說是件好事
I like being on my own. I'm better off this way.
我喜歡一個人過生活 我喜歡這個樣子
I'm a lone wolf.
我是一匹孤獨的野狼
A loner. Alone.
我是個完全孤單的硬漢
All alone. Forever.
永遠都是一個人
What's a wolf gotta do to get a hug around here?
狼要怎麼做 才能得到一個擁抱呢？
That's it, just relax.
好了，放輕鬆
-Come on, more. -Oh, God!
-加油，再來 -天啊
You like that, don't you?
你喜歡那樣，對吧？
-Yeah, right there. -Want it there? Take it there, baby.
-對，就是那樣 -你要嗎？我就給你，寶貝
-Phoebe? -Yeah, say my name. Say it.
-菲比 -對，叫我的名字，快點
And now I'm going to cover you back up.
現在我要幫你 蓋上被子
And I won't be speaking with you for several weeks.
我會有好幾個星期 不會再跟你說話